- 我回来了   - 嘿
- Hi, you guys.     - Hey.
怎么了？
What's the matter?
又是那种很讨厌的状况
Well, it's just... It's one of these situations that I just hate.
有一个客人给我三张票
You know, a massage client gave me three tickets...
去摩根大通博物馆看展览
to the Helmut Peltz Exhibit at the Morgan Chase Museum.
所以你觉得你得跟他上床
Now you're thinking you gotta sleep with him.
不是 他给我三张票 但是我们有六个人
No. No, it's just that he gave me three tickets and there are six of us.
- 我弃权   - 我也是
- I'll give up my ticket.     - Me too.
你们真大方
Okay. That's so generous.
罗斯应该也很大方
And I think Ross is generous too.
太好了 那我们女生自己去
Great. Okay. Then it's just us girls.
- 太好了   - 赞
- Great.     - Yeah.
是什么展览？
So, what is the exhibit?
主要是女同志的...
It's mostly just photographs...
性爱摄影展 还可以打电动 吃免费三明治
of, um, lesbian love scenes interspersed with video games and free sandwiches.
都是你
Oh, man.
- 大家好   - 嘿
- Hi.     - Hi. Hi there.
罗斯
Hey, Ross, listen.
钱德说你周末 不想去女同志三明治博物馆
Chandler got you out of going to the lesbian sandwich museum this weekend.
谢谢 我有节目了 伊丽莎白和我要出城去
Thanks? But I have plans. Uh, Elizabeth and I are going out of town.
- 太好了   - 对啊
- Oh, that's great.     - Yeah.
你可以藉此大赚一笔
Think about all the money that you're gonna make.
什么意思？
Why? What?
是她爸找你去当保姆对吧？
Well, her father pays you for babysitting, right?
- 哦   - 哈哈
- Uh-oh.     - Ha, ha.
真好笑 但你们也该有所长进
No, no. That's funny. But maybe it's time to move on.
够了 别再闹了
You know, let it go. Stop it.
况且瑞秋在和她爸交往
Besides, Rachel's going out with Elizabeth's father.
而他比她大多了
So, uh, he's much older than she is.
看来不只是我对化石有兴趣
Looks like I'm not the only one interested in fossils. Huh?
罗斯 这种话只会提醒我们 你对化石有兴趣
Ross, all that does is remind us that you are interested in fossils.
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
嗯 瑞秋想和他甜言蜜语 可得用吼的
Uh, well, Rachel's gonna need to yell sweet nothings in his ear. Huh?
- 罗斯   - 拜托 这很好笑啊
- Ross?     - Oh, come on, that's funny, you know?
因为他戴助听器 因为...
Because he's got, like, a hearing aid, you know?
因为他很老
Because he's all old.
失陪一下
One second.
听着 罗斯
Okay, look, Ross.
因为丽莎很喜欢你
Just so you know, since Lizzie likes you so much...
我决定接受你们交往的事
I accept the fact that you're going out with her.
真的？太好了
Really? Okay, that's great.
是啊 但后来我又反悔了
Yeah. But then I changed my mind.
我就是这么善变
I'm funny like that.
我已经告诉她 现在我告诉你
So I've told Lizzie and now I'm telling you.
我不希望你再和我女儿见面
I don't want you seeing my daughter anymore.
好 我知道你很不高兴
All right, look. I realize it upsets you.
没错
Yes, it does.
但伊丽莎白和我都是成年人
But Elizabeth and I are both adults...
所以你也莫可奈何
and so I don't think there's really anything you can do about it.
我会告诉学校你们在交往 让你被开除
I'll tell the university about your relationship and have you fired.
有备而来喔
Oh, a man with a plan.
老友记 第六季 第二十二集
好兴奋喔 你的照片又要重回名人墙了
This is so exciting. You get your picture back up on the wall of fame.
就是啊 之前在墙上时好快乐
I know. It was so cool when it was up there before.
我经常和吉姆贝路西说笑
Me and Jim Belushi would just be cracking up about something.
后来我被《我们的日子》开除 照片被拿下来
Then I get fired off Days of Our Lives and he takes me down.
现在他都在嘲笑我
Now he's just laughing at me.
你看那个自鸣得意的混蛋
Look at him. That smug Belushi bastard.
也许他们可以
Oh. Okay. Maybe when they put your picture back up...
把你挂在麦特劳尔旁边
they could put you next to Matt Lauer.
你看他在对我微笑
Look at him just smiling at me. Hee-hee.
我知道 我们会很速配
Yeah, I know. We'd be great together.
- 我回来了   - 你是谁？
- Hey. So I'm back.     - Who are you?
乔伊崔比亚尼
Joey Tribbiani.
我之前上过墙
From the wall?
也许这样你会想起来
Okay, maybe this will jog your memory, huh?
嗯？
Huh?
总之...
Okay, anyway.
我可以回墙上了 我主演了一出新戏
I'm ready to go back up on the wall. I'm the star of a new TV show.
- 哪出？指给我看   - 还没上档
- Show me in the TV book.     - Oh, well, it's not on TV yet.
那你就还不能上墙
Well, then it's not on the wall yet.
好吧 我拿录影带给你看
Okay, fine. I will bring you a tape. Huh?
你手边有麦特劳尔的衣服吗？
So, um, now, do you have any of Matt Lauer's clothes here?
还没洗过的？
Maybe just ones that haven't been cleaned yet?
天啊
God.
我好喜欢来博物馆
I love museums.
- 接受文化薰陶   - 是啊
- Soaking up all the culture.     - Yeah.
- 要先去哪里？ - 礼品贩卖部
- Where do you want to start?     - Ooh, the gift shop.
对啊
Yeah.
- 然后去吃饭 好   - 但我不能吃太多
- Hey, and then lunch.     - Oh, wait, yes, but I can't eat too much.
保罗今晚要带我去吃饭 他说会有个大惊喜
Paul's taking me out to dinner tonight. He said he has a big surprise planned.
他会不会要说他是同性恋？
Ow, wow. What do you think? Maybe he's gonna tell you he's gay?
什么？为什么？
What? No, why?
不为什么 那样真的会很惊奇
No reason. That would just be a really big surprise, right?
红毯可以铺在这边 然后在这边证婚
You could put the aisle over here and then have the wedding ceremony here.
原来这里可以结婚
I didn't know you could get married here.
这里当礼堂的确很美
This would be a beautiful place to get married.
但我不会把红毯铺在那边 更不会在那边证婚
Yeah, but I wouldn't put the aisle there. And I'd never have the ceremony there.
应该在这个漂亮的拱门下证婚
You'd have the ceremony under this big, beautiful arch.
有什么事吗？
May I help you?
抱歉打断你 这里很美
Oh, sorry. Didn't mean to interrupt. It's a beautiful space.
- 经常举办婚礼吗？ - 是的 这里很受欢迎
- Do you do a lot of weddings here?     - Yes, we're very popular.
预约已经排到两年后 抱歉
There's a two-year waiting list. Sorry.
摩妮卡 你也应该去预约
Monica, you should totally put your name down for this place.
什么？你疯了吗？
What? Are you crazy?
我又不结婚 我甚至还没订婚
I'm not getting married. I'm not even engaged.
但反正要等两年 要是你两年后订了婚
Yeah, but there's a two-year wait. What if you get engaged in two years?
还得再等两年
Then you've gotta wait another two years for this place?
那就四年了 钱德才不会等那么久
That's four years. Chandler's not gonna wait that long.
他会去找别人
He's gonna find somebody else, you know?
- 某个有预约礼堂的人   - 嗯
- Someone who put their name on the list.     - Mm-hm.
先预约又不会怎样
Yeah. Honey, it can't hurt to put your name down.
要是两年后没订婚就放弃不用
If in two years you're not engaged, you just don't use it.
先预约的确不会怎样
Well, I guess there is no harm in putting my name down.
- 我也要预约   - 我也要
- I'm gonna do it too.     - Me too.
真的？你要嫁给谁？
Really? Who would you marry?
不知道 我现在还没有对象
I don't know. I don't have anyone right now, you know?
噢 菲比
Oh, Pheebs.
别为我难过 至少我的男朋友不是同性恋
Don't feel too sorry for me. At least my boyfriend isn't gay.
- 菲比 你根本...   - 别逼我批评你家那个
- Phoebe, that's not...     - Don't even get me started on yours.
- 你看过录影带了吗？ - 看过了
- So, did you watch the tape of my show?     - I did.
- 好 让我回墙上吧   - 不行 你不能上墙
- All right. Let's get me back up there.     - No. You don't go up on the wall.
- 但你看过我的戏了   - 对 那冒犯了我的同胞
- What? But you saw the show.     - Yes. It was very offensive to my people.
干洗店老板吗？
Dry cleaners?
俄国人 它把他们当成恐怖分子和坏蛋
Russians. It showed them as terrorists and villains.
好 你看 你有哈里逊福特
Okay, okay. Look, you got Harrison Ford up there.
没错 福特先生是个好顾客
That's right. Mr. Ford is a very good customer.
他带很多衣服来 你两手空空
He brings us a lot of clothes. You bring us nothing.
或许吧
Okay, well, that may be true.
但在《空军一号》里 俄国人是恐怖分子 很邪恶
But in Air Force One, okay, the Russians were terrorists and evil.
他还杀了一堆俄国人 那样很冒犯你们
And plus, he kills a bunch of them. That's offensive to Russians.
- 我没看过   - 你应该要看 很赞
- I've never seen it.     - Oh, you should. It's great.
这里真的好漂亮
This place is really beautiful.
对啊 我从小就常来 这里以前是我奶奶家
Yeah. I've been coming here since I was a kid. This used to be my grandma's.
我只遗传了我奶奶的眼睛
Wow. The only thing I got from my grandmother was her eyes. Heh.
我不是说她的眼珠子
I mean, not her actual eyeballs.
但是大家都说我的眼睛...
But people say that my eyes look...
- 你要不要亲热？ - 好啊
- Do you want to make out?     - Sure. Ha, ha.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
- 怎么了？ - 呃...
- What's wrong?     - Uh...
我只是想到你爸爸
Yeah, I was just thinking about your father.
- 只要能让你兴奋就好   - 不是
- Well, whatever works for you.     - No.
不是 他有点把我吓到了
No, no. Uh, he just really freaked me out before.
噢
Oh.
我们得再多瞒着一个人
Well, so we have to hide our relationship from one more person.
那又怎样？况且我们也喜欢这样躲藏
Big deal. Besides, we've had fun hiding it.
也对
Yeah.
- 怎么了   - 没事
- Hey.     - Yeah.
你有准备防护措施吗？
Um, you brought protection, right?
怎么了？这里有熊吗？
Why? Are there, like, bears or something?
- 不是   - 哦 呃...
- No.     - Oh, uh...
你是说那个 没有 我忘了
Oh, protection, yeah. No. That I forgot.
那我去买
Ha, ha. I'll just run to the store and get some.
不 我是男人 我去买
No. Hey, hey. I'm the guy. I'll get it.
- 你知道商店在哪里吗？ - 不知道
- Do you know where the store is?     - No.
你想骑粉红脚踏车逛大街吗？
Do you want to ride around town on my little pink bicycle?
有点想
A little bit.
- 我十分钟后回来   - 好
- I'll be back in 10 minutes.     - Okay.
你先进浴池里等我
Why don't you get in the hot tub and I'll meet you there.
好
Oh, okay.
天哪 好棒的惊喜 这栋房子好漂亮
Oh, my God. What a great surprise. This is such a beautiful house.
谢谢 这是我妈的房子 这里是厨房
Thank you. It used to be my mother's. So this is the kitchen.
这里是摩妮卡和钱德的家
You've reached Monica and Chandler's.
如果你听到这则留言 我们可能在过滤电话
If you're listening to this message, we're probably screening.
没错
Yeah, we are.
我是摩根大通博物馆的希蒂
Hi, this is Hildy from the Morgan Chase Museum.
我要找摩妮卡盖勒
I'm calling for Monica Geller.
有人取消预约
I want to let her know there was a cancellation.
如果她还想在我们这里办婚礼
If she's still interested in having the Bing-Geller wedding at our facility...
现在有空了
it is available.
我是钱德宾 我是钱德宾
This is Chandler Bing. This is Chandler Bing.
是的 我是新郎 不 我不是
Yes, the groom. No, not the groom!
这里好幽静
It's so secluded up here.
- 我知道 所以我喜欢这里   - 嗯
- I know. That's why I like it here.     - Mm-hm.
全世界好像只剩我们两个人
I feel like we're the only two people in the world.
抱歉
Whoops. Sorry.
怎么了 宝贝？
What's the matter, honey?
- 你看到老鼠了吗？ - 不是 大熊 外面有大熊
- Did you see a little mouse?     - No. Big bear. Big bear outside.
我想我...
I think I...
你要不要... 要不要去看一下？
Actually, would you go check on that?
亲爱的 这里没有熊
Honey, we don't have any bears here.
好吧
Well, okay.
帮我倒杯健怡可乐 好吗？
Would you get me a Diet Coke?
- 好 我马上回来   - 好
- Okay. Be right back.     - Okay.
- 你在这里干嘛？ - 你又在这里干嘛？
- What are you doing here?     - What are you doing here?
- 我是跟保罗来的   - 我认出他的脚踝了
- I came with Paul.     - Yeah. I recognized the ankles.
快出来
Hurry up. Get out.
拿来了
Here you go, honey.
- 谢谢你   - 健怡可乐
- Ah. Thank you.     - Diet Coke.
冰块
Oh. Ice.
我需要冰块
I need ice.
好
Okay.
- 谢谢你   - 我马上回来
- Thank you.     - Be right back.
好
Okay.
- 又是冰块这一招   - 噢
- You and your ice.     - Oh.
出来 出来 快点
Get out. Get out. Go. Come on.
快点
Quick.
不行 不行 他在那里面
No, not in there! Not in there! He's in there!
- 你真的听到熊叫了吗？ - 进去啦
- Did you really hear a bear?     - Go!
来了
Here you go, honey.
一杯加冰的健怡可乐
One Diet Coke with ice.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
真高兴有你在
I am so happy that you're here.
- 我回来了   - 伊丽莎白
- Here I am.     - Elizabeth.
看 伊丽莎白来了
Oh, look. Elizabeth's here.
你在跟谁说话？
Who were you talking to?
你们啊
You guys?
你怎么知道我们在这里？
How did you know we were here?
- 嗯...   - 她定是看到...
- Um...     - Well, she obviously saw the tire tracks...
往车库的方向有轮胎痕
that were leading up to the closed garage.
当然
Obviously. Heh.
伊丽莎白 你来这里干什么？
Elizabeth, what are you doing here?
你是来这里赶报告的吗？
Did you come up here to work on that term paper or something?
没错
Yeah. Yeah.
那你去那个房间写吧
Well, why don't you, you know, go in that room and do your homework?
我不会去那个房间写 那是我爸的卧房
Oh, I wouldn't do it in there. Um, that's my dad's bedroom.
那是你爸的卧房
That's your dad's bedroom.
Ha, ha. That's your dad's bedroom.
嚯嚯
Ho-ho.
- 你干嘛这么大声？ - 哦
- Why are you yelling?     - Oh!
健怡可乐让我好嗨
That Diet Coke, I think, went straight to my head. Whoo!
亲爱的
Hi, honey.
待会儿见
See you later.
我买了东西要帮你煮晚餐
Wait. I bought groceries. I was gonna make you dinner.
下次先问我
Well, next time, ask.
或等我先开口
Or at least wait for me to ask.
我是摩根大通博物馆的希蒂
Hi, this is Hildy from the Morgan Chase Museum.
我要找摩妮卡盖勒
I'm calling for Monica Geller.
完了
Oh, no.
有人取消预约
I wanna let her know there's been a cancellation.
如果她还想在我们这里办婚礼
If she's still interested in having the Bing-Geller wedding at our facility...
现在有空了
it is available.
拜托 他没听到 他没听到
Please. He didn't hear it.
我是钱德宾 我是钱德宾
This is Chandler Bing. This is Chandler Bing.
不
No!
有什么事吗？
Can I help you?
决定谁能上墙的那个人呢？
Uh, yeah. Where's the guy who decides whose pictures go up on the wall?
- 他现在不在   - 不会吧
- He's not here right now.     - Oh, you're kidding me.
记得告诉他
All right, well, make sure you tell him that
乔伊崔比亚尼带了一堆衣服来
Joey Tribbiani dropped off these clothes.
我是个演员 我想让我的照片上墙
Okay? I'm an actor. I'm trying to get my picture up there on the wall.
其实有两个人能决定这件事
You know, there are two people who could get your picture up there.
是吗？
Oh, really?
也许我们应该去喝一杯
Well, maybe you and I go out for drinks.
你是另外一个人吧？
You're the other one, right?
丽莎 你今晚要留下来过夜吗？
So, Lizzie, are you planning on staying the night?
不 我要尽快离开
Oh, no, no. Believe me, I'm leaving as soon as possible.
那好...不是我们不要你留下来 我们当然很欢迎你
Good, good. Not that we don't want you to stay. Obviously, you're welcome.
你还有多少功课？
How much more homework do you have?
只剩一个问题 我不知道怎么解决
Uh, I just have one problem left that I do not know how to solve.
瑞秋 也许你可以上楼来帮我
Uh, Rachel, maybe you want to come upstairs and help me figure it out?
是吗？
Really?
好
Okay.
好 我上楼
Okay, I'll go upstairs...
你去车上帮我拿东西
if you get me something from the car.
你要拿什么东西？
What do you need from the car?
给我惊喜啊
Surprise me.
- 好啊   - 好
- Okay.     - Okay.
你要去车上 我要去楼上
So you're gonna be in the car. I will be upstairs.
这就是目前的状况
And that's where everybody's gonna be.
放轻松 放轻松 保罗 你表现得很好
Just relax. Just relax, Paul. You're doing great.
她喜欢你
She likes you. She...
我想她喜欢你 她喜欢你
I think she likes you. She likes you.
为什么？因为你粉赞
You know why? Because you're a neat guy.
你是男子汉
You are the man.
还是很有料
Still got it.
很性感
Still sexy.
你是个爱情机器
You're just a love machine.
我是个爱情机器
I'm just a love machine
为你所拥有的自豪 宝贝
So proud of what you have, baby
上场了
Showtime.
我是个爱情机器 宝贝
I'mjust a love machine Hey, baby
- 菲比   - 什么事？
- Phoebe?     - Yeah?
- 你有见到钱德吗？ - 没有 怎么了？
- Have you seen Chandler?     - No, why?
博物馆那个女人打来说 有人取消预约
The woman from the museum called and said that there was a cancellation...
我们可以提前举行婚礼 结果钱德听见了
and we could move up our wedding. Chandler heard.
就是啊 你觉得有多严重？
I know. How bad is this?
对一般男人来说很严重 但是对钱德...我的天哪
Well, with a regular guy, it's bad. With Chandler, oh, dear God.
我知道 他被吓到了 我到处都找不到他
I know. I know. He totally freaked out and I can't find him anywhere.
- 你要怎么办？ - 反正我再也不听你的话了
- Well, what are you gonna do?     - I'm never listening to you again, for sure.
"先预约又不会怎样"
"What harm can it do to put your name down?"
- 那是瑞秋说的   - 瑞秋不在这里
- Rachel said that.     - Well, Rachel's not here!
在这里
Ooh, here it is.
乔伊 你为什么要签"混蛋"？
Ooh, Joey, why did you sign it, "son of a bitch"?
（混蛋）
- 我没有啊 这是谁干的？ - 混蛋
- I didn't do that. Who would've done that?     - Son of a bitch.
问他好了
Okay. Maybe ask this guy.
你 滚出我的店
You. Get out of my shop.
- 他做了什么？ - 他跟我老婆约会
- What did he do?     - He went out with my wife.
- 乔伊   - 哇哦 哇哦
- Joey.     - Whoa, whoa, whoa.
我没有跟你老婆约会 好吗？
Hey, I did not go out with your wife. Okay?
- 我是跟她约会   - 她就是我老婆
- I went out with her.     - That's my wife.
滚
Get out!
- 我们还是走好了   - 对
- Well, we should go.     - Yeah.
罗斯？
Ross?
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth.
好 我从窗户爬出去
Okay. Okay. I'm gonna go out this window.
我们前门见
I'll meet you at the front door.
- 你就说你要回家   - 好
- Just tell them you're going home, okay?     - Okay.
等等 别进去
Wait, wait. No, don't go in there.
我还要喝汽水
Don't go in there. I need another soda.
罗斯
Ross.
天哪 罗斯 你在这里干什么？
Oh, my God. Ross, what in heaven's name are you doing here?
所以我们不能再见面了
And that is why we cannot see each other anymore.
罗斯 我们得好好谈一谈
Ross, you and I are gonna have to have a little talk.
- 爸...   - 接着就是你
- Daddy, I...     - You're next.
好 我不知道他来了
Okay. I didn't know he was here.
让我把话问清楚
Let me just see if I got this straight.
我叫你离我女儿远一点 否则就要你被开除
I tell you to stay away from my daughter or I'll have you fired.
结果你听到的是 "带我女儿...
What you heard was: "Take my daughter...
到我乡下的别墅 破坏我和瑞秋的周末"
come up to my country house and ruin my weekend with Rachel."
- 拜托 请听我说   - 不 你听我说:开除
- Okay. Please, Paul. Just let me explain.     - No. Let me explain. Fired.
好 开除就开除
Okay, fine. Fine. Have me fired.
我只想让你知道...
But, uh, I want you to know...
你跟我也没差那么多
that you and I are not all that different. I mean...
我也粉赞
I, too, am a neat guy.
什么？
What?
我也是...
And I, too...
爱情机器
am just a love machine.
罗斯...
Ross.
我带你去客房
Let me show you where the guest room is.
对不起 你别再害怕了
I'm so sorry. Please stop freaking out.
我没有害怕啊
I'm not freaking out.
我干嘛害怕？
Why would I freak out?
有个叫希蒂的说我们要结婚了
A woman named Hildy called and said we were getting married.
但这是常有的事
But that happens every day. Ah-ah-ah!
亲爱的 那个地方很漂亮
Honey, we were at this beautiful place.
我只是预约好玩的
And I just put our names down for fun.
- 会怎样吗？ - 会这样
- I mean, what's the harm in that?     - Right here.
钱德 千万别以为我想逼婚
Please don't think I was trying to pressure you.
- 菲比和瑞秋觉得...   - 菲比和瑞秋？
- Phoebe and Rachel just thought...     - Phoebe and Rachel?
所以比我早知道 我们要结婚的 有你...
So the people that knew about our wedding before me were you...
菲比和瑞秋 希蒂...
Phoebe and Rachel, Hildy...
和一个叫《星光魔力》的乐团
and apparently some band called Star Light Magic Seven...
对了 他们也有空
who are available, by the way.
我错了
It was a mistake.
我完全没有那个意思
Please don't take this to mean anything, because it doesn't.
好吧
Okay.
真的吗？
Really?
如果你真的没有那个意思 你知道我还没准备好
Yes. If it really doesn't mean anything, because you know I'm just not ready.
我知道
I know.
好
Okay.
All right.
我去告诉乔伊你回来了
Now, I'm gonna go tell Joey that you're back.
我们刚才好担心
We were really worried about you.
- 她相信了吗？ - 相信了
- Hey, did she buy it?     - Totally.
- 希蒂有带你参观吗？ - 有 那里好漂亮
- So did Hildy show you the place?     - Yeah. It's beautiful.
你居然要跟摩妮卡求婚了
I can't believe you're gonna ask Monica to marry you.
就是啊
I know.
- 阿甘   - 把这些卡布奇诺瑞到十一桌
- Hey, Gunther.     - Take these cappuccinos to Table 11.
那个男的要意大利脆棒
And that guy over there wants some biscotti.
我只是要外带一杯咖啡
Oh. Well, I just actually came in for a cup of coffee to go.
你还在这里工作吗？
Do you still work here?
没有 我早就不做了
No, no. I quit a long time ago.
我没有告诉你吗？抱歉
Did I forget to tell you that? I'm sorry.
- 算了 反正我也打算开除你   - 太好了
- Oh, it's cool. I was gonna fire you anyway.     - Great.